

MOUAD BELGHAZI

Business & Marketing Student

- +34 659 782 560
- O Toledo, 45007, Spain
- mouad.belghazi24@gmail.com
- 🗎 24 December 2001, Moroccan



Mouad Belghaz

SKILLS

- Digital Marketing
- Digital communication
- Organizational skills
- Team spirit
- Marketing
- Website creation
- E-commerce website
- Digital Marketing Tool

LANGUAGES

- ARABIC (Native language)
- English (Fluent)
- FRENCH (Bilingual)
- SPANISH (Beginner)

INTERESTS

- Travel
- Passion for fitness
- Passion for foreign cultures
- Passion of learning

ABOUT ME

I'm a motivated marketing and business student with practical experience in affiliate marketing and digital marketing gained through various jobs and studies. I'm highly adaptable, proactive and trustworthy when it comes to carrying out my missions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Affiliate Marketer and team leader

11/2020 - 09/2023

SM Media Solution I Tangier, Morocco

- I was responsible for leading email marketing campaigns, managing team tasks, preparing and filtering campaign data, creating promotional materials, generating leads, and identifying lucrative marketing opportunities.
- Coordinating the marketing team to develop effective and innovative promotional campaigns.

Community Manager

03/2020 - 09/2023

GeoBox Africa I Tangier, Morocco

My role was to manage the online community and enhancing the brand's digital presence.

EDUCATION

Master's degree in Business Strategy and Marketing University of Castilla La Mancha, Toledo, Spain 2023 - 2024

Bachelor's degree in Economics and Managment University of Abdelmalek Essaadi, Tangier, Morocco 2019 - 2021

Training in web development
Solicode digital training center in Tangier
2021 - 2022

Training in web development Simplon.co digital training center 2021 - 2022